Shreya Pandey

Public Relations And Advertising

My goal is obtain a job in public relations or marketing where i can utilise my skills and education in both written and verbal communication and experiences such as writing, styling and editing. i also hope to employ some of my natural talents such as hard work, dedication and creativity in a position that will allow me to learn and grow.

Work History

2023-03 -2023-05 Influencer Marketing Intern, Wellcurve

Vrushika Singh, Delhi

2022-06 -2022-08 **PR Intern Royal Fables**

Anshu Khanna, Delhi

Worked as a PR Intern

Did styling for a photoshoot

Handled an entire photoshoot as a project head

Pitched advertising ideas for labelled brands

https://www.instagram.com/reel/CgT2JetsQOZ

/?igshid=MzRIODBiNWFIZA==

https://www.instagram.com/reel/CgT2JetsQOZ

/?igshid=MzRIODBiNWFIZA==

https://www.instagram.com/reel/CgjqT7tgEBv

/?igshid=MzRIODBiNWFIZA==

https://www.instagram.com/reel/CgrQ57QuiTG

/?igshid=MzRIODBiNWFIZA==

https://www.instagram.com/reel/Cgz\$dLyJAAD

/?igshid=MzRIODBiNWFIZA==

2021-06 -2021-07

Social Media Intern, Fitlook Magazine

Mohit Kathuria , Delhi

- Reviewed articles for grammar, spelling, punctuation, syntax, accuracy, and compliance with quality.
- Prepared, rewrote, and edited pieces to improve readability and impact.
- Pitched content strategies



Contact

Address

Noida, India 201301

Phone

8826585814

E-mail

seventeenpandeyshreya03 @gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com /in/shreya-pandey-8128781b

WWW

https://bold.pro/my/shreya-pandey-230730190558/107

Skills

Styling

SEO Writing

Press Releases

Media Relations

Content Writing

Editing(Canva, Lightroom)

2020-04 -2020-09

Pyro Media

Influencer Marketing Intern, Delhi

- Built and maintained positive business relationships with clients while advocating for company in Type negotiations.
- Discussed marketing goals with clients to identify needs and articulate details to marketing team.
- Led implementation of best practices to support customer service satisfaction initiatives.
- Cut delivery times through proactive tracking and monitoring of project timelines and aggressive pursuit of customer approval of digital and print files.

Education

2020-07 -2023-05 **BAJMC: Mass Communication**

Bennett University - Greater Noida

Interests

Fashion

Art

Politics

Creative Writing

Exploring

English Proficiency- Written and Spoken

Affinity Publisher

Excellent communication skills

Podcasts

Languages

English



Spanish

